Dog River Has Always Been Flat. But Now It's Flat Broke.
Corner Gas: The Movie is a family, comedy film directed by David Storey.
It’s been a few years, and there’s still not a lot
going on 40 kilometers from nowhere.
But that’s all about to change as the fine folks of Dog River,
Saskatchewan face their biggest crisis ever.
Brent and the gang discover that the town’s been badly mismanaged,
leaving residents with little choice but to pack up and leave.
As residents make one last rally to save Dog River as they know it, they discover a devious
plan by a corporate chain that would change life for Dog Riverites forever.
Brent Leroy, played by Brent Butt.
Lacey Burrows, played by Gabrielle Miller.
Hank Yarbo, played by Fred Ewanuick.
Oscar Leroy, played by Eric Peterson.
Emma Leroy, played by Janet Wright.
Davis Quinton, played by Lorne Cardinal.
Corner Gas: The Movie is a 2014 Canadian comedy film directed by David Storey
and is based on the television series Corner Gas (2004-2009).
The film stars Brent Butt, Gabrielle Miller, Fred Ewanuick, Eric Peterson, Janet Wright, Lorne Cardinal, Tara Spencer-Nairn,
Nancy Robertson, Cavan Cunningham, Gwen Seed and Jean Freeman all reprising their roles from the television series.
The film also features new characters played by Don Lake, Reagan
Pasternak, Graham Greene, Will Sasso and Karen Holness.
The original series aired on  CTV from 2004 to 2009.
The film gained a limited release, and was later released on DVD and Blu-ray.
Fans of the television series reacted positively to the
film, which led it to gain a cult following.
This was Janet Wright's final performance before her death in 2016.
The tone is lighthearted.